[welcome to Comfyui Tutorials by iimate24]
Today, I will try to install ComfyUI manually. You can use it without using a script.
What do you type? We use Runpod, and today we are using Runpod Command Line at
Terminal, which we are now in this workspace directory is the workspace.
So the first thing we're going to do is copy the comfyui Github directory.
I think my friends probably have this link. The way to do it is to come here and press this button: copy to clipboard.
Then we come back to our terminal page in runpod. How to install Runpod, etc.
I think most of my friends can do it already, but if it's a new friend, try going back and looking at
This is the first episode of the series so the download method is easy, we will use the word
Say Git clone and then Ctrl + V the link that we copied and Enter on the left hand side here.
A ComfyUI folder pops up indicating that we have successfully downloaded it, but
If it is still downloading, please wait here for it to finish. After a while, the download speed will be around the same.
Download speed of this is around 900 MB per second on the server I use.
Now, I am using RTX5080 with 83 GB RAM, but the graphics card RAM is 16 GB. The download is complete.
And it will look something like this. Next, we will create a Virtual Environment.
Use the command python -m venv myvenv
Then followed by the name of the virtual environment.
What we want to set, let's say we want to set today as myvenv.
Then press Enter and this folder will be created.
folder virtual environment which we can name it as anything we want
We want but when we call we will call us by using command to activate source my
venv bin and then activate we will use this command
That is, we will have a folder called activate inside this folder if we double-click on it.
Click myvenv in bin
And then in here, there will be a file called
activate We will call this file. Press activate. We will have comfyUI.
We have the environment, then we have to install it.
install ComfyUI using this command, scroll down the mouse, we will select here because we use
Nvidia GPU cards now have 2 commands, the first command of the person using the normal version
In general, you can just copy this. But for me, I will install the Nightly version and it is for
For 50xx graphics cards, we will copy this directly and paste it into the command line.
After installing, when it installs, it will work like this in the background. It will load.
Many files are coming down, and this step should take about 20 minutes.
Okay, the installation is complete. If it comes up like this, it means it's done.
Once done we can continue working. You will notice that it downloads the package.
Various things to use in comfyUI, namely a list of everything it has.
install See? But we haven't finished installing it yet. We still have to install the requirements.
ComfyUI's too, and the way to use it is 1. We have to go into the ComfyUI Folder.
What you do is type the word CD and then type C because Python, um, Linux is like that.
Like case sensitive, it means big and small.
Type in lowercase c, we will not see it. Type in C and press tab once, we will see it automatically.
complete stay here Enter this is the command now we are in the folder of
comfyUI How to see the details inside, press ls -la and then we press Enter, which we
I want to see what files it has, which we need is requirement.txt.
Inside here, in this file, we can actually see it in requirements. We double-click.
From here, you can see the details inside. See? These are the packages that we need to install.
But when we install, we don't have to install them one by one. We don't have to type install one by one.
Use the command pip install -r requirement.txt
install and then there is a delete r which is delete r which is it will automatically install every package that it puts in.
When you come here, we call the file name. Requirements are the same as before. Press the small r.